Mr. School
Responsibility
Responsibility What are you?  Why is it?
Even if you have less sleep, don't have too much salt.   It is
your nature to come late.
Whoever is with you, how will he be your time companion?
Okay brother, sometimes a plumber, sometimes an electrician, she
teaches me by making mistakes, she makes me do so many things,
responsibility
comes before every thought, the thought of someone else
[music], she
thinks for someone else first, wow,
responsibility
lifts me up, makes me fall
and even when I want to stop,
you are the one who encourages me.   Hey,
this is responsibility, you are very lovely.
Life is made of responsibilities and is for these
lovely responsibilities.  ICICI
Piden Life Insurance Responsibility is
dear.